=============================================

X

Privacy Policy
--------------

This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) describes Rise Platforms Ltd.’s (“we,” “us,” or “our”) privacy practices with respect to your use of our website, available at: [http://rise-platforms.com/](http://rise-platforms.com/) (the “Website”).

Please also review the Terms of Service (the “Terms”) available at: [http://rise-platforms.com/terms-of-service/](http://rise-platforms.com/terms-of-service/)

We note that you are not legally required to provide us with any personal information, and may do so at your own discretion. If you do not wish to share your personal information with us, or to have it processed by us or our services providers (set forth in Section 2.3) as further described in this Policy, or if you disagree with any of the terms set forth herein, please refrain from using or accessing the Website.

1\. Information We Collect and Purposes of Collection
=====================================================

1.1 Information we collect:

1.1.1  General Information collected upon your use of the Website. We may use and collect technical information from your device, including your device type, browser and operating system, IP address and additional similar technical information automatically collected when you visit or interact with our Website. We may also collect information regarding your interactions with our Website.

1.1.2   Information you voluntarily provide us. If you choose to communicate with us, we will maintain a record of your communication with us in order to provide you with support services, collect your email address, and, if applicable, investigate the issues raised by you. We do not use information you voluntarily provide us for advertising purposes.

1.2   Purposes of the collection of your information:

We use personal data as necessary for the facilitation and performance of our Website; to comply with our legal and contractual obligations; and to support our legitimate interests in maintaining and improving our Website, providing services and technical support, and protecting and securing our Website’s visitors and otherwise individuals who interact with us.

If you reside or are using the Website in a territory governed by privacy laws under which “consent” is the only or most appropriate legal basis for the processing of personal data (in general, or specifically with respect to the types of personal data you expect or elect to process or have processed by, or via the Website), providing such personal data and using the Website, as well as your acceptance of our Terms and this Policy will be deemed as your consent to the processing of your personal data for all purposes detailed in this Policy. If you wish to revoke such consent, please contact us at [legal@rise-platforms.com](mailto:legal@rise-platforms.com).

Specifically, we use personal data for the following purposes:

1.2.1 Operating the Website – developing, operating, improving and expanding the Website.

1.2.2 Analytics – Generate reports and analytics.

1.2.3 Internal operations – to support our internal operations, including internal debugging.

1.2.4 Updates – to provide you with updates related to the Website.

1.2.5 Compliance – to comply with any applicable laws and regulations.

2\. Sharing and Disclosure of Information
=========================================

2.1. General. We will not sell, rent or share your personal data except in specific circumstances as described in this Policy or if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is permitted by law or is reasonably required to: (i) comply with any law, legal requirement, process or regulation, including without limitation, court orders, subpoenas,  or other compulsory disclosures, or to maintain, establish, or exercise our legal rights; (ii) enforce this Policy or the Terms; (iii) protect our rights or (iv) prevent, investigate,  or take action regarding illegal activities or violation of third party rights (whether suspected or actual); or. In addition, in the event that of a bankruptcy, acquisition, merger, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred.

2.2. Our Corporate Affiliates. We may disclose your information to our corporate affiliates to receive services, such as storage, security, IT and other internal operations.

2.3. Our Service Providers. We may be using third party software and/or services in connection with the operation of the Website. We may disclose your information to such authorized third-party service providers for business purposes. The third parties we are currently engaging are:

* Amazon Web Services, Inc. servers to store your information. The measures taken by Amazon to protect the security of their servers and your information are detailed at: [https://aws.amazon.com/security/](https://aws.amazon.com/security/).

3\. Data Location & Retention
=============================

Data Location. We operate globally and your personal data may be maintained, processed or stored by us and our service providers in multiple locations, such as Israel, the United States, Europe, or other jurisdictions, as reasonably necessary for the proper performance and delivery of the Website, or as may be required by law.

While privacy laws may vary between jurisdictions, we and our service providers are each committed to protect personal data in accordance with this Policy, reasonable and customary industry standards, and such appropriate lawful mechanisms and contractual terms requiring adequate data protection, regardless of any lesser legal requirements that may apply in the jurisdiction to which such data is transferred.

Data Retention. We will retain your personal data for as long as it is reasonably necessary for us to maintain and expand our relationship and provide you with Website or other services; in order to comply with our legal and contractual obligations; or to protect ourselves from any potential disputes (i.e., as required by laws applicable to financial solutions, log-keeping, records and bookkeeping, and in order to have proof and evidence concerning our relationship, should any legal issues arise following your discontinuance of use), all in accordance with our contractual terms and data retention policy.

Please note that except as required by applicable law or our specific agreements with you (if any), we will not be obligated to retain your personal data for any particular period, and we are free to securely delete it or restrict access to it for any reason and at any time, with or without notice to you.

4\. Data Subject Rights
=======================

Please send us an email to: [legal@rise-platforms.com](mailto:legal@rise-platforms.com) if you wish to exercise your privacy rights under any applicable law, including the EU or UK General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA), the California Privacy Rights Act (CPRA), or the Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act (VCDPA). Such rights may include, to the extent applicable, the right to know/request access to (specific pieces of personal information collected; categories of personal information collected; categories of sources from whom the personal information was collected; purpose of collecting personal data; and categories of third parties with whom we have shared personal data), to request rectification or erasure of your personal data held with us, your right to restrict or object to such personal information’s processing, or to port such personal information or the right to equal services and prices (e.g., freedom from discrimination) (each to the extent available to you under the laws which apply to you). If you are a GDPR-protected individual, you also have the right to lodge a complaint with the relevant supervisory authority in the EU or the UK, as applicable.

Subject to applicable privacy laws, we will make reasonable efforts to accommodate your request. Please note, that before we take any action, we may ask you to provide us additional information, including personal data, in order to authenticate and validate your identity and process your request.

5\. Our Policy Towards Children
===============================

The Website is not directed and/or intended to persons under the age of 13. We do not collect personal data from any person we actually know is an individual under the age of 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal data, please contact us at [legal@rise-platforms.com](mailto:legal@rise-platforms.com).

6\. Security
============

We employ industry standard measures, procedures and policies to ensure the safety of our site visitor’s personal data, and to prevent unauthorized use of any information. Please note that regardless of the measures and efforts taken by us, we cannot and do not guarantee the absolute protection and security of your information.

7\. Requirements Under US States Privacy Laws.
==============================================

This Policy describes the categories of personal information we may collect and the sources of such information, our retention and deletion practices. We also included information about how we may process your information, which includes for “business purposes” under the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA)/California Privacy Rights Act (CPRA) and similar state laws, as applicable. We do not sell your personal information for the intents and purposes of the CCPA or CPRA. We may share (as such term is defined under the CPRA) personal information with third parties if we have an appropriate contractual terms with the business that controls the collection of the shared personal information. We may also disclose personal information with third parties that are authorized Service Providers or business partners who have agreed to our contractual limitations as to their retention, use, and disclose of such personal information. You may also designate an authorized agent, in writing or through the power of attorney, to request to exercise your privacy rights on your behalf. The authorized agent may submit a request to exercise these rights by emailing us via [legal@rise-platforms.com](mailto:legal@rise-platforms.com). We will not discriminate against you by withholding our services from you or providing a lower quality of service to you for requesting to exercise your rights under the law.

If you have any questions or would like to exercise your rights under any applicable US State privacy laws, you can contact us via [legal@rise-platforms.com](mailto:legal@rise-platforms.com).

8\. Changes to This Policy
==========================

We may update this Policy from time to time so please visit this page regularly. If we make changes that are material, as shall be determined in our sole discretion, to the way we treat your personal data, or to the Policy, we will make reasonable efforts to provide you with notice through the Website, or by any other means. Your continued use of the Website constitutes your complete and irrevocable acceptance to any updated Policy. If any changes made to the Policy are not acceptable to you, you may cease using the Website.

9\. External Links
==================

The Website may contain links to other websites or services. This Policy does not apply to such linked third-party websites and We are not responsible for such websites’ or services’ privacy practices. Please read the privacy polices of each website you visit, before providing any personal data.

10\. Contact Us
===============

If you have any questions or comments about the Policy, please contact us at [legal@rise-platforms.com](mailto:legal@rise-platforms.com).

© 2023 Rise Platforms

Menhcem Road 121  
Tel Aviv  
Israel

Company
